A Guide to the Office of the Messrs. Rockefeller records, Educational Interests, Series G FA316
Rockefeller Archive Center
- International House
  - International House, Chicago, 1929-1938 (Box 17, Folder 110)
    Preliminary survey of Chicago site; purchase of property; pledge for building; remitting funds, arranging payments and taxes. Invitations to meetings and formal events. Correspondents include Raymond B. Fosdick, Willard S. Richardson.
    60.2
  - International House, Chicago, 1927-1936 (Box 17, Folder 111)
  - International House, Chicago - Dorchester Avenue Property, 1929-1936 (Box 18, Folder 112)
    Management of property. Heydt and Fosdick trustees for John D. Rockefeller, Jr. Sold to University, 1935. Correspondents include Charles O. Heydt, Raymond B. Fosdick, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., John D. Rockefeller 3rd.
  - International House, Chicago, 1939-1960 (Box 18, Folder 113)
    Programs of Chicago House; John D. Rockefeller 3rd small contributions toward special projects. Air Force use of House during war. Changes in personnel. David Rockefeller attended 25th Anniversary program. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., John D. Rockefeller 3rd, David Rockefeller, Adlai Stevenson, E. B. Price.
  - International House, Chicago, 1955-1960 (Box 18, Folder 0113A)
  - International House, Chicago - Tablet, 1936-1938 (Box 18, Folder 0113B)
    Location of tablet tribute to John D. Rockefeller, Jr. at Chicago House.
  - International House, Chicago - Pledges and Contributions, 1928-1943 (Box 18, Folder 114)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s gifts for purchase of land and construction of building.
  - International House, Chicago, 1927-1931 (Box 18, Folder 115)
  - International House, Chicago, 1932-1943 (Box 18, Folder 0115A)
  - International House, Boston, 1930-1934 (Box 18, Folder 116)
    Charles O. Heydt and Raymond B. Fosdick trustees for property on Charles River Esplanade. Management of property, treatment of tenants; National Recovery Act (NRA) code. Decision made not to build House in Boston. Attempts to sell property. Correspondents include Charles O. Heydt, Raymond B. Fosdick, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Boston Real Estate agents.
    60.3
  - International House, Boston, 1935-1943 (Box 18, Folder 0116A)
  - International House, Boston - Trust Agreement, 1930-1940 (Box 18, Folder 0116B)
    Trustees held property for John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
  - International House, Boston - Sale of Land to Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1936-1942 (Box 18, Folder 117)
    Many unsuccessful attempts to sell property through Boston brokers. In 1942 property sold to Massachusetts Institute of Technology at great loss; savings realized in tax structure. Correspondents include Charles O. Heydt, Raymond B. Fosdick, John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
    60.3B
  - International House - International Students Association of Greater Boston, 1947-1955 (Box 18, Folder 118)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr. declines involvement in Association on the basis that his contributions to International House fulfilled his obligation in that direction. John D. Rockefeller 3rd gives $20,000, 1953. Correspondents include Arthur W. Packard, Edgar B. Young, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., John D. Rockefeller 3rd, L. M. Mead, Jerome D. Greene.
    60.31
  - International House Association, 1947 (Box 19, Folder 119)
    An association coordinating Houses in Chicago, New York, and Berkeley. Selection of an executive; incorporation and planning; temporary director. Leon de Rosen appointed director. Organizational politics. David Rockefeller active in program to increase educational activity of International Houses; his speech, November 11, 1949. Contributions by David Rockefeller, John D. Rockefeller 3rd, Nelson A. Rockefeller. de Rosen's resignation. Chapters of Association in other countries. 1953, David Rockefeller reduces his support of Association. Herrick Young resigns as director; changes in Association, 1958. International Conference in Paris, 1961; David Rockefeller attended. Correspondents include David Rockefeller, John Mott, R. Sproul, Leon de Rosen, Herrick Young.
    60.4
  - International House Association - Correspondence, 1947 (Box 19, Folder 0119A)
  - International House Association, 1947-1961 (Box 19, Folder 0119B)
  - International House Association, 1948 (Box 19, Folder 120)
  - International House Association, 1949 (Box 19, Folder 121)
  - International House Association, 1949 (Box 19, Folder 0121A)
  - International House Association, 1948-1949 (Box 19, Folder 122)
  - International House Association, 1950-1951 (Box 19, Folder 123)
  - International House Association, 1951 (Box 19, Folder 0123A)
  - International House Association, 1951-1953 (Box 20, Folder 124)
  - International House Association, 1954-1956 (Box 20, Folder 0124A)
  - International House Association, 1957-1961 (Box 20, Folder 0124B)
  - International House Association - International Quarterly, 1948-1955 (Box 20, Folder 125)
    David Rockefeller articles in Quarterly.
  - International House Association - Director, 1947-1948 (Box 20, Folder 126)
    Selection of temporary and permanent directors.
  - International House Association - Contributions, 1947-1960 (Box 20, Folder 127)
    Contributions for special purposes by David Rockefeller, John D. Rockefeller 3rd, Nelson A. Rockefeller.
  - International House Association - Re: Mrs. Melson, 1947-1948 (Box 20, Folder 128)
    Mrs. Melson sent to survey European conditions prior to organization House there. Reports from various places in Europe. Correspondents include David Rockefeller, John D. Rockefeller 3rd, John Mott.
  - International House Association - Re: Mrs. Melson, 1947-1948 (Box 20, Folder 129)
  - International House Association - Mexican Chapter, 1948-1951 (Box 20, Folder 130)
    David Rockefeller's interest in helping organize a Mexican chapter. Plans in Mexico City. John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Mrs. Roosevelt, President Alemas made honorary members of chapter. Correspondents include David Rockefeller, J. Mott, Leon de Rosen.
  - International House Association - Charter, By-Laws and Incorporation, 1947 (Box 20, Folder 131)
    Revisions of by-laws. Copy of Certificate of Incorporation.
  - International House Association - Charter, By-Laws and Incorporation, 1948-1951 (Box 20, Folder 132)
  - International House Association - A. Jones Survey, 1949 (Box 21, Folder 133)
    Jones makes special study of budget and program of International House Association. Point of departure a survey by outside consultants. Correspondents include A. Jones.
  - International House Association - A. Jones Survey, 1949 (Box 21, Folder 0133A)
  - International House Association - Tamblyn and Brown Survey, 1949 (Box 21, Folder 134)
    A study of House alumni in areas affecting future House policies. Financed by David Rockefeller. Arthur W. Packard comments on findings. Correspondents include David Rockefeller, Arthur W. Packard.
  - International House Association - Tamblyn and Brown Survey, 1949 (Box 21, Folder 0134A)
  - International Houses - Suggested Sites, 1930-1961 (Box 21, Folder 135)
    Plans for Houses in United States, Japan, Germany, France, Australia, Formosa, Austria, Hawaii. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., John D. Rockefeller 3rd, Arthur W. Packard, Harry Edmonds.
    60.5
  - International Houses - Suggested Sites, 1947-1961 (Box 21, Folder 0135A)
  - International House - India International Center, 1958 (Box 22, Folder 136)
    Rockefeller Foundation assists in building center in New Delhi. John D. Rockefeller 3rd very interested in progress and program; his trip to India in 1959. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller 3rd, Dean Rusk, D. H. McLean.
    60.7
  - International House - India International Center, 1959-1961 (Box 22, Folder 0136A)
- National Kindergarten Association
  - National Kindergarten Association, 1913-1942 (Box 22, Folder 137)
    Requests for aid in initiating kindergartens throughout United States. Rockefeller office consistently declined. Correspondents include Willard S. Richardson, Arthur W. Packard.
    123.1
- Fringe Benefits Organizations
  - Fringe Benefits Organizations - United Parents Association, 1926-1958 (Box 22, Folder 138)
    Organization to bring closer cooperation between home and school. John D. Rockefeller, Jr. made small donations, 1926-1934. Organization watched by staff, but no further donations. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Arthur W. Packard, Nelson A. Rockefeller.
    72
  - Fringe Benefits Organizations - Parents League of New York, Inc., 1945-1956 (Box 22, Folder 139)
    A parents association for independent schools. Laurance S. Rockefeller and Mary French Rockefeller, and John D. Rockefeller 3rd and Blanchette Hooker Rockefeller members. Membership cancelled when children left schools. Correspondents include Arthur W. Packard.
    72.1
  - Fringe Benefits Organizations - Parents League of New York, Inc., 1949 (Box 22, Folder 0139A)
  - Fringe Benefits Organizations - Department of Education, New York City, 1921-1960 (Box 22, Folder 140)
    Small contributions to special activities of various New York schools and for special surveys. Correspondents include Arthur W. Packard, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Laurance S. Rockefeller, Nelson A. Rockefeller.
    72.2
  - Fringe Benefits Organizations - Department of Education, New York City - Elias Lieberman, 1944-1951 (Box 22, Folder 0140A)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s interest and approval of "Code of Behavior Voted by Students." Followed development of manual for students.
  - Fringe Benefits Organizations - Public Schools Athletic League, 1906-1933 (Box 22, Folder 141)
    Contributions by John D. Rockefeller and John D. Rockefeller, Jr. to promote "useful athletics and gymnastics" among children in New York Public Schools. Correspondents include Starr J. Murphy, Willard S. Richardson.
    72.3
  - Fringe Benefits Organizations - Public Schools Athletic League, Girls Branch, 1910-1961 (Box 22, Folder 142)
    Contributions by John D. Rockefeller, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Abby Aldrich Rockefeller, Martha Baird Rockefeller to program.
    72.4
- Schools
  - Schools - Miscellaneous (A-C) (Box 23, Folder 143)
    Miscellaneous appeals for aid. Most declined, since General Education Board and Rockefeller Foundation represented family's interest in education. Occasional small contributions for special purposes. Some gifts by John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s children to schools which their children attended. Some small contributions by the 4th generation. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Willard S. Richardson, Arthur W. Packard, Dana S. Creel, Laurance S. Rockefeller, Nelson A. Rockefeller, David Rockefeller, John D. Rockefeller 3rd, W. Buttrick, E. M. Hopkins.
    Alexander Hamilton High School, 1948 Alfreda Madison Project, 1953 Allen-White High School, Tennessee, 1939-1948 Altaraz Project (International School), 1946 American Foundation for Sang Myung School, Korea, 1954 American School Foundation, Mexico, 1950 Anglo-American School of Oruro, Bolivia, 1952-1960 Arizona Desert School, 1931-1954 Arizona Ranch School, 1960 Arroyo Grande Union High School, California, 1950 Asian School of Public Administration, 1955 Avery Training School (retarded children), 1959 Balala High School, Philippines, 1948 Bettis Academy, South Carolina, 1955 Bishop Payne Divinity School (Negro education), 1944 Booker T. Washington High School, 1954 Boys Vocational School - Methodist Church Gulfside Assembly Advance Movement (Negro education), 1949-1950 Brantwood Hall School, 1944 Brooklyn Friends School, 1948 Browne & Nichols School, Massachusetts, 1930-1931 Brownell School, Cleveland, 1951 Calhoun School, New York City, 1955 Calvert School, Maryland, 1937-1955 Chestnut Hill Academy-Springside School, Pennsylvania, 1955 Church Farm School, 1961 Citizens Committee for Better Public School, New Jersey, 1950 Clear Creek Mountain Preachers Bible School, Kentucky, 1952 The Clearing, 1945-1948 Coalhurst School, 1961 Colegio San Ignacio de Loyola, Puerto Rico, 1954 *Collegiate School, New York City, 1940-1956 Colorado Rocky Mountain School, 1953-1954 *Cutler School, New York City, 1922-1924
    * indicates that the school received a Rockefeller contribution.
    175
  - Schools - Miscellaneous (D-E) (Box 23, Folder 0143A)
    Dalton School, 1952 Dana Hall School, 1946 Mr. Dargan Project, Negro Education, Georgetown County, South Carolina, 1947 Divine Savior High School, Wisconsin, 1948-1951 Downingtown Industrial School, Pennsylvania, Negro education, 1949 Dubois Grammar School, Wyoming, Mary Allison, 1955 Ecole Polytechnique Summer Program, 1948-1961 Englewood School for Boys, 1949
  - Schools - Miscellaneous (F-I) (Box 23, Folder 144)
    Fieldston School, New York, 1947 Fishburne-Hudgins Educational Foundation, 1951 Fork Union Military Academy, 1941-1942 Foster School of Fine Arts, 1948 Foxcroft Academy, 1949 Franklin Development Foundation, 1951 Free Schools Committee, New Mexico, 1948 Germantown Academy, Pennsylvania, 1936-1958 Graham-Eckes School, Florida, 1950 Greenwich High School, 1961 Groton School (John D. Rockefeller, Jr. recommendation for Ralph Bunche, Jr.), 1956 Hannah Harrison School, 1954 Hebron Academy, 1958 Henry George School of Social Science, 1935-1949 Hermetic School of Occult Wisdom, 1954 High School of Music and Art, New York City, 1958-1960 Hessian Hills School, New York, 1931-1951 Highlander Folk School, Tennessee, 1950 Hill School, 1956 Hogan Institute of Technology (Negro education), 1946-1962 Holly Point, Lake Murray Education Center, South Carolina (Negro education), 1947 Holy Innocence Church School, New York, 1954 *Home Efficiency School, 1919 Horace Mann School, New York City, Charles Tillinghast, 1951 Hospital Hill School, Kenya, 1956 Hudson River Country Day School, Tarrytown, 1959 Hudson River Naval Academy, New York, 1947 Huguenot Society Vocational Farm School, 1940 Indian Mountain School, Connecticut, 1939-1951 Iolani School, Hawaii, 1960 Irving School, Tarrytown, 1955
  - Schools - Miscellaneous (J-L) (Box 23, Folder 145)
    Jackson Hole Summer School, 1954 *Juilliard School of Music, 1949-1957 King-Smith Studio School, 1944 Lake Forest Academy, Illinois, 1947-1950 Lakewood School, New Jersey, 1956 Lane College, Tennessee, 1949 Lawrenceville School, 1957 Leicester Academy, New York, 1940-1943 Lomax-Hannon Industrial College (Negro education), 1948 Lexington School for the Deaf, 1961 Longy School of Music, Massachusetts, 1961
  - Schools - Miscellaneous (A-L) (Box 23, Folder 0145A)
    *American Community School of Paris, 1957 American Institute for Foreign Trade, 1950-1961 Archbishop Stepinac High School, New York, 1947-1959 Arthur Sweetser Project (International School), 1949 Bedford Rippowam School, New York, 1947 Brooklyn Friends School, 1948 Brooks School, Massachusetts, 1950-1952 Buckingham School Fund, 1949-1950 California School of Fine Arts, 1959-1960 *Carmelite Priory, Tarrytown, New York, 1955 Dobbs Ferry High School, New York, 1951-1958 Ecole Polytechnique Summer Program, 1948-1961 Episcopal Academy for Girls, 1954-1957 Fountain Valley School, 1961 Frank Gerard Project (International School), 1947 *Graham Home for Orphans, 1948-1960 Lake Forest Academy, Illinois, 1947-1950 Laurinburg Normal and Industrial Institute, North Carolina, 1952 Lovett School, Georgia, 1960 Lycee Francais de New York, 1959
  - Schools - Miscellaneous (M-O) (Box 24, Folder 146)
    Marion King Project, 1933 Maryland Institute, 1951 *The Masters Nursery, New York City, 1954-1961 The Masters School, 1947-1955 Metropolitan Music School, 1961 *Mill Neck Manor, School for the Deaf, 1955-1960 *Millbrook School for Boys, New York, 1946-1961 *Milton Academy, New York, 1937-1961 *Montgomery Country Day School, Pennsylvania, 1959-1961 Montverde School, Florida, 1950 Mountain Mission School, Virginia, 1944-1950 New Era Theological Institute, Pennsylvania, 1953 New York State Schools - Report of the Regents' Inquiry into the Character and Cost of Public Education in the State of New York *North Country School, 1950-1961 North Park School, New York, 1953-1958 *North Tarrytown High School, 1917-1919 Northampton School for Girls, 1960 *Nursery School, New York City, 1958 Oakwood School, New York, 1958 Oneida Institute, 1930-1940
  - Schools - Miscellaneous (P-R) (Box 24, Folder 0146A)
    Pacific Oaks Friends School, California, 1958 Parsons School of Design, 1953 Peddie School, New Jersey, 1951 Penland School of Handicrafts, 1951 Penn School, South Carolina (Negro education), 1949 Pennsylvania Military College, 1929-1935 Percy Houston Project, 1933-1934 Perdue Hill Industrial School, Alabama (Negro education), 1958 Philadelphia Divinity School, 1938-1939 Philadelphia Textile Institute, 1946-1958 Portsmouth Priory, Rhode Island, 1939-1947 Powhatan County Schools, Rosa L. Martin, 1948 Pratt Institute, New York City, 1954-1960 Protestant School in Damascus, 1952 Public Schools, Fauquier County, Virginia, 1946 Roger Ascham School, New York, 1930-1934 Roosevelt School (clipping), 1948 Russell Ranch School, Arizona, 1949-1950
  - Schools - Miscellaneous (S) (Box 24, Folder 147)
    St. Andrew's School, Florida, 1961 St. Bernard's School, New York, 1950 St. George's School, Rhode Island, 1958 St. John's Indian Mission School, 1947 *St. Louis Country Day School, 1953-1954 St. Mary's of the Valley Academy, Oregon, 1952 St. Mary's Parish School, New York City, 1948 St. Mary's School, New York, 1949 St. Mary's School, Colorado, 1930-1935 *St. Paul's School, New Hampshire, 1956 St. Theresa School, New York, 1926-1941 S Sarah Tucker Schools, India, 1956 Save Leland and Gray Fund, 1946-1947 Sawyer College, 1943-1944 School of Advanced International Studies, 1955-1958 School of World Citizenship and Democracy, Dr. W. Seiferth, 1946 Sevenoaks School, 1954 Shady Hill School, 1946 Sisters of Mercy, Rhode Island, 1950 Spencerian College (Cleveland), 1927-1942 Stratford Junior High School, Virginia, 1956 Suffield Academy, Connecticut, 1948
  - Schools - Miscellaneous (T) (Box 24, Folder 0147A)
    Takana Farm High School, India, 1959 Tamalagon Primary School, Philippines, 1950 Tarrytown School, 1955 Technion, 1948-1952 Textile Industrial Institute, North Carolina, 1930-1941 *Thayer Academy, Massachusetts, 1952-1953 Thetford Academy, New Jersey, 1948 Thompson Academy, Massachusetts, 1958 Toccoa Falls Institute, Georgia, 1942 Todhunter School, New York City, 1938 Transfiguration School, New York, 1949 Trinity Lutheran Church, Iowa, 1947 Trinity School for Boys, New York City, 1943-1946
  - Schools - Miscellaneous (U-W) (Box 24, Folder 148)
    Ursuline Convent, British Columbia, 1954 Valley Forge Military Academy, Pennsylvania, 1948 Vermont Academy, 1954 Viewpoint School, New York, 1950 Walden School, New York City, 1954 Walsingham Academy, Virginia, 1949-1959 *Walter D. Matheny School, 1952-1960 Ward-Belmont School, 1951 *Washington Irving High School, New York, 1933-1960 Wayside Inn School, Massachusetts, 1948 Western Cavite Institute, Philippines, 1953 Wooster School, New Jersey, 1951
  - Schools - Miscellaneous (M-P) (Box 24, Folder 149)
    Miscellaneous appeals for aid. Most declined, since General Education Board and Rockefeller Foundation represented family's interest in education. Occasional small contributions for special purposes. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Willard S. Richardson, Arthur W. Packard, Dana S. Creel, Laurance S. Rockefeller, Nelson A. Rockefeller, David Rockefeller, John D. Rockefeller 3rd, W. Buttrick, E. M. Hopkins.
    Marlboro School of Music, Vermont, 1959-1960 Maryland Institute, 1951 *Mill Neck Manor, School for the Deaf, 1955-1960 *Millbrook School for Boys, New York, 1946-1961 *Milton Academy, Massachusetts, 1937-1961 *Montgomery Country Day School, Pennsylvania, 1959-1961 *North Country School, 1950-1961 *Nursery School, New York City, 1958 Panamerican School, Mexico, 1957 Panorama Baptist Elementary School, California, 1954 Philadelphia Textile Institute, 1946-1958 *Phillips Academy, Massachusetts, 1937-1961 Pilgrims School, England, 1956 *Potomac School, Virginia, 1946-1961 Pratt Institute, New York City, 1954-1960
  - Schools - Miscellaneous (R-W) (Box 24, Folder 149A)
    Rudolf Steiner School, New York City, 1943-1955 Ruth Maxwell Project - American School in Tangier, 1950 St. Hilda's School, New York City, 1955-1957 *St. Vincent Ferrer's Church, New York City, 1948-1949 School of Advanced International Studies, 1955-1958 *Shipley School, Pennsylvania, 1960 *Town School, 1954-1962 Townsend Harris High School, New York City, 1954 Walden School, New York City, 1954 Waldorf School, Germany, 1952 *Washington Irving High School, New York, 1933-1960
  - Schools - North China Union Language School, Peking, 1922-1946 (Box 24, Folder 150)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr. and Laura Spelman Rockefeller Fund contributions to building fund for school teaching Chinese language; breach between school and academic circles. Name changed to College of Chinese Studies. Correspondents include Dr. H. C. Fenn, W. P. Petters, H. E. Fosdick, Arthur W. Packard, Willard S. Richardson, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., John D. Rockefeller 3rd.
  - Schools - Maine Nautical Training School, 1939-1941 (Box 24, Folder 151)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr. advises Mr. Getchell on establishment of school to train boys for merchant marine. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Arthur W. Packard, Lawrence B. Getchell.
  - Schools - Pine Lodge School, 1919-1943 (Box 24, Folder 152)
    Attended by Laurance S. Rockefeller and John D. Rockefeller 3rd; horses for the boys. Olmstead's financial difficulties; John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s annual gifts, 1932-1937; Laurance S. Rockefeller and John D. Rockefeller 3rd gifts, 1938-1942. Correspondents include Frank Olmstead, Charles O. Heydt, Roswell Miller, John D. Rockefeller 3rd, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Arthur W. Packard.
  - Schools - Miscellaneous - "OUT" Cards (Box 24, Folder 0152A)
    North Haven High School, 1960; St. Christopher's, New York (neglected children), 1960
  - Schools - Middle East Institute, 1949-1961 (Box 25, Folder 153)
    Reports on Institute; appeal to Winthrop Rockefeller for assistance declined. Correspondents include Christian Herter, Philip Watts, Dana S. Creel, Arthur W. Packard, Winthrop Rockefeller.
  - Schools - Foreign Service Educational Foundation, 1944-1949 (Box 25, Folder 154)
    Report on Foundation sponsoring School of Advanced International Studies; C. Herter's report on foreign service training. School attacked for pro-Arab policies. Nelson A. Rockefeller's nonrecurring contributions. Correspondents include Christian Herter, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Arthur W. Packard.
  - Schools - Palmer Memorial Institute, North Carolina, 1909-1956 (Box 25, Folder 155)
    Private school for Negroes; requests aid but John D. Rockefeller, Jr. declined on ground that General Education Board recommends that school merge with public school system (whites unwilling to pay taxes for public Negro schools while Northerners support private Negro education). Difficulties in merger with public school system. John D. Rockefeller, Jr. declines further appeals; Abby Aldrich Rockefeller's annual contributions, 1930-1948. Correspondents include Dr. Wallace Buttrick, Dr. Charlotte Brown, John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
  - Schools - Mooseheart, 1921-1955 (Box 25, Folder 156)
    Order runs orphanage school at Mooseheart. John D. Rockefeller, Jr. declination of invitation to become Life Member of Loyal Order of Moose. Order appeals for contributions for school; General Education Board reports; John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s nonrecurring anonymous contribution, 1924; further appeals declined. Correspondents include James J. Davis, Thomas B. Appleget, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., T. Arnett.